{
    "id": "cb59decd9239487e969b9ea74741bd3f",
    "title": "Since And For",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been associated with this organization ………………… ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother has been ailing …………………. July.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… when have you been living in this city?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They have been learning Latin ………………….. six months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister has been learning music …………………. January.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked as a waiter ………………….. six years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been practicing Yoga ………………….. six years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… when have you been learning music?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We have been living in this city ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been ten years ………………… I retired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}